John Mack is going to protect you . . . whether you want him to or not.
The Guardian is a drama, thriller film directed by David Greene.
The residents of a New York apartment building are shocked
when one of them is shot during a burgulary.
They decide to hire a security expert to patrol the building,
but he seem a little over-committed to his work.
Charlie Hyatt, played by Martin Sheen.
John Mack, played by Louis Gossett Jr..
Dr. Phil Julian, played by Arthur Hill.
Lynn Hyatt, played by Tandy Cronyn.
Robbie Hyatt, played by Simon Reynolds.
Mr. Wicker, played by Tom Harvey.
The Guardian is a 1984 American thriller film directed by David
Greene and written by Richard Levinson and William Link.
The film stars Martin Sheen, Louis Gossett Jr., Arthur Hill,
Tandy Cronyn, Simon Reynolds and Tom Harvey.
The film premiered on HBO on October 20, 1984.
The tone is emotional and intense.